<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/CTF_Adventures/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/CTF_Adventures/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-12-22T22:45:01+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/CTF_Adventures/</id><title type="html">CTF Adventures</title><subtitle>CTF Adventures. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Thoughts…</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/CTF_Adventures/jekyll/update/2017/12/22/Thoughts.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Thoughts..." /><published>2017-12-22T16:54:07+08:00</published><updated>2017-12-22T16:54:07+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/CTF_Adventures/jekyll/update/2017/12/22/Thoughts</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/CTF_Adventures/jekyll/update/2017/12/22/Thoughts.html">&lt;p&gt;When I was first introduced to CTF, I know nothing about it. I was just a mere script kiddie. (skiddie? I think I still am one..)
I was introduced to jeopardy style CTF in 2016, and it really caught my attention. It was not just about “cracking a system”, but it was a computer puzzle in a form of Computer Security.
It requires the knowledge of Computer Security in order to solve challenges to get flags. CTF has become my new “game”, and I sign up for every single online CTF availble. (even if the challenges were way out of my league. for the lols maybe?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will be participating in an upcoming offline CTF called JDC - Junior Defender Camp. Organized by &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ntu-offsec&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;NTU OffSec&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Fingers crossed and hopefully I can solve all the challenges.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">When I was first introduced to CTF, I know nothing about it. I was just a mere script kiddie. (skiddie? I think I still am one..) I was introduced to jeopardy style CTF in 2016, and it really caught my attention. It was not just about “cracking a system”, but it was a computer puzzle in a form of Computer Security. It requires the knowledge of Computer Security in order to solve challenges to get flags. CTF has become my new “game”, and I sign up for every single online CTF availble. (even if the challenges were way out of my league. for the lols maybe?)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My First Post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/CTF_Adventures/jekyll/update/2017/12/22/First-Post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My First Post" /><published>2017-12-22T16:54:07+08:00</published><updated>2017-12-22T16:54:07+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/CTF_Adventures/jekyll/update/2017/12/22/First%20Post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/CTF_Adventures/jekyll/update/2017/12/22/First-Post.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello readers. I go by the name &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gladitor&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; on CTFtime.org. I’m new to CTF, and this blog would be the place where I will documenting my adventures and personal write ups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My past adventures includes &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;TUCTF&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;inCTF&lt;/code&gt;. Currently practicing &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Web&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Reverse Engineering&lt;/code&gt;. If you have advice on those, I would be happen to hear from you!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: The screen name &lt;strong&gt;*Gladiator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; was the name that I used for online-games. Hence, I adopted it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello readers. I go by the name Gladitor on CTFtime.org. I’m new to CTF, and this blog would be the place where I will documenting my adventures and personal write ups.</summary></entry></feed>